Besiege is this game where you spend hours on the perfect machine. Then it collapses, and explodes!
I've seen people beat levels with a few blocks as possible, like a bunch of lazy scrubs!!
So today I'm going to show you how to beat all the levels with as much stuff as I can fit.
Leveeeeel 1: Destroy a house.
Easiest way would just be to put wheels on something and drive into it
But hell no! I know wheels are considered one of the great inventions.
It's up there with fire and mouthwash but my great-great-great ...
...Great-great-great-great grandfather knew the guy who invented the wheel, and he was the biggest douche in Mesopotamia
So let me introduce you to the future of transport based shapes: the square
gg! Leveeeel 2: a windmill.. The famous antagonist of Spanish Literature.
This beast is terrifying. Those sails reek of death!
But there is an old Dutch saying: the only thing that can defeat a windmill... is a bigger windmill!!
*boink*
You've got to be kidding me. Bigger windmill with missiles. ={
Level 3: the Minefield
The problem is Besiege you can't steer without using the steering function.
But I consider that hacking, so to get through we need to build an unstoppable force!
That is not fireproof. To make it fireproof we can use water cannons, but that gave me a better idea:
What if we treat the bombs like
protesters!? This game is way too easy!
Level: Windmill!! BRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR!!
So I guess windmills can't defeat bombs. This could work!
I said 'could' work.
We need water cannons, so I saved the car
But I still couldn't defeat those houses. The only thing that can help us now is more water cannons
I... I have no idea how I did that. We've played for nine hours
And finally reached level five: kill an army. The game has weaponry. This would be way too easy
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. The weapons were useless. Time to find an alternate solution... Besiege...
Besiege... Besieeged...
Besiege D!
*Gas Gas Gas plays*
Level: Balls.
Grab the balls and dip 'em in the right place, so we need to create something with hands.
We'll put a stick here, stick here
Maybe add a fan and boom this guy could really use a spine and using a forklift was pointless because I.. I
Don't have a driver's license. I'm tired of creating new stuff. Can't I just use what I have?
I can!
That's when he understood that this is the ultimate machine
I will beat every level using the power of water cannons.
Nope, it's a laser rock
I surrender, I surrender!! Leveeel seveeeeen
We'll put rocks on explosives, then they will fly all over the place, killing everything including the laser stone
Few games can make me lose the ability to be disappointed
How would I destroy a stone in real life? Of course!
I would use a pickaxe!
Aww yeah, once again Minecraft has helped me more than school. Level eight: stone house
Destroy with explosives
Uhh I'll just use a missile?
My God... it has some sort of missile defense shield!
Catapults? It's impossible to hit! I have no choice. I need to blow up the entire map.
Smashing a couple of atoms together creates a very big bomb.
Maybe I can recreate that using a couple of rubber bands and two logs
I have a PhD in physics. Level... ??
Tents. Soldiers. Cannons. This isn't a level... this is war. And I know war...
*Ride of the Valkyries plays*
~This is the end my only friend the en-dahhhh~
~Da-da-duh plans...~
Level ten: the final challenge. And by that I mean have been playing for 30 hours now
And I give up. Destroying this sissy
Instrument will be the hardest challenge of them all. I know what I have to do: combine all the things I have into one
Super creation, and this is as far as I got before my computer melted. Fuck it! [I'm] spawning a robot dinosaur
What what's he doing? He's flying away!
Ohhh... Right! Dinosaurs used to be birds. What a
beautiful creature. I was completely obsessed with beating besiege, but this
Dinosaur completed the hardest challenge of them all...
He followed his dreeeaammsss.